

EDUCATION

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Green Fox Academy 2022 - 2023

TEACHING OF HISTORY AND ETHICS

Constantine the Philosopher University in Nitra 2016 - 2021

LANGUAGE

SLOVAK

C2

ENGLISH

C1

GERMAN

B2

Phone

0944 162 840

Email

tomas.hecko96@gmail.com

Born

15. 6. 1996

Address

Nábrežná 93 / 5 940 02, Nové Zámky Slovensko

MGR. HEČKO TOMÁŠ

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm young, curious and passionate Full-Stack developer who likes to have a challenge, methodically and structuraly approach different problems and then solve them. I've been always interested into tech-related stuff since my younghood. I have built my first programs being 16 years old using Delphi or built a custom Wordpress page with different plugins. Currently I work in a Fin-Tech sphere on a Full-Stack project. I thrive to be better at what I do everyday, trying to figure out how to do it in better way while still enjoying the challenge that comes with it.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2023 - now FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CRIF - Slovak Credit Bureau, s.r.o.

2021 - 2022 MACHINE OPERATOR

AGRO TAMI a.s., NITRA

TECH STACK

Angular JS, Typescript, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS

- pre-intermediate
- creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components based on documentation from the customer
- creating custom, general use modules and components which extend the elements and modules of core AngularJS
- cooperating with the back-end infrastructure in the process of building the RESTful API

Java 11, Spring Boot, Maven, Junit, JPA

- pre-intermediate
- create endpoints which are responsible for different CRUD operations based on REST API
- designing & developing back-end components of web applications via Spring Boot
- sending back different kinds of responses based on structure of the application (JSON / XML)
- creating and running unit / integration tests
- debugging the software and testing applications

AWS, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Helm, Flyway, Docker

- beginner
- basic knowledge of how CI/CD works
- mostly profficient with K8s CLI, working with pods and their configuration and deployment

Git, GitBash, CLI, Versioning

- intermediate
- creating, modifying repositories, working with remote / local branches
- rebase, head, tag, merge conflict, merging, branching

LINKS

LINKED IN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomashecko/

GITHUB: https://github.com/TomTom258

PERSONAL WEBPAGE: https://tomtom258.githb.io/Personalized-CV/